(Penny:)Every family in America has a relative...
(Penny:)...holed up in a garage somewhere
huffing paint thinner.
(Howard(after Raj whispers in his ear):)No, I'm lost too.
I think she skipped a step.
Now, look, Sheldon's cousin Leo escaped
rehab and he's in a Motel 8 in Long Beach.
(Penny:)The whole family's going out
for an intervention.
(Penny:)Leonard is driving Sheldon down
to help him through this...
(Penny:)- ...because he's such a good man.
- Oh, another hug? Thank you.
- All right, you guys. Good luck.
- Thanks, Penny.
(Howard:)- Break a leg.
- Yeah, break a leg.
(Howard:)So road trip to Long Beach.
(Leonard:)- We're not going to Long Beach.
- Why not?
(Leonard:)Because Sheldon doesn't have
a drug-addicted cousin Leopold.
(Penny:)Oh, too bad.
(Raj:)I've always wanted to go to Long Beach.
(Sheldon:)It's a very nice community.
The Queen Mary is docked there.
Once the largest liner in the world,
it's now a hotel and restaurant...
(Sheldon:)...where they host a surprisingly gripping
murder-mystery dinner.
- Sounds fun.
- I'm game.
- Shotgun.
- No, no, no.
(Sheldon:)Leonard gets nauseous unless
he sits in front, and even then it's iffy.